associateprograms.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy policy | AssociatePrograms.com

If information is being gathered about you, I believe you have a right to know.

AssociatePrograms.com does not collect information on its website visitors such as names, addresses, telephone numbers, or email addresses – unless you specifically give AssociatePrograms.com that information.

AssociatePrograms.com does not sell or otherwise make available email addresses to anyone except Aweber.

If you have any questions about your privacy while using AssociatePrograms.com, please [contact us](https://www.associateprograms.com/contact-us "Contact Us").

Here's the legal jargon version.

* * *

**Protecting your private information is our priority.**  This Statement of Privacy applies to the www.associateprograms.com and Zed Seven Pty Ltd ATF The Stockwell Family Trust and governs data collection and usage. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, unless otherwise noted, all references to Zed Seven Pty Ltd ATF The Stockwell Family Trust include www.associateprograms.com and Zed Seven. The Zed Seven website is a Affiliate Education & Media site. By using the Zed Seven website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.

**Collection of your Personal Information**  
Zed Seven may collect personally identifiable information, such as your name. If you purchase Zed Seven's products and services, we collect billing and credit card information. This information is used to complete the purchase transaction. We may gather additional personal or non-personal information in the future.

Information about your computer hardware and software may be automatically collected by Zed Seven. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the Zed Seven website.

Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through Zed Seven's public message boards, this information may be collected and used by others.

Zed Seven encourages you to review the privacy statements of websites you choose to link to from Zed Seven so that you can understand how those websites collect, use and share your information. Zed Seven is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on websites outside of the Zed Seven website.

**Use of your Personal Information**  
Zed Seven collects and uses your personal information to operate its website(s) and deliver the services you have requested.

Zed Seven may also use your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from Zed Seven and its affiliates. Zed Seven may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.

Zed Seven does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties.

Zed Seven may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is transferred to the third party. Zed Seven may share data with trusted partners to help perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to Zed Seven, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.

Zed Seven may keep track of the websites and pages our users visit within Zed Seven, in order to determine what Zed Seven services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within Zed Seven to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.

Zed Seven will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Zed Seven or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Zed Seven; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Zed Seven, or the public.

**Use of Cookies**  
The Zed Seven website may use “cookies” to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize Zed Seven pages, or register with Zed Seven site or services, a cookie helps Zed Seven to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same Zed Seven website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the Zed Seven features that you customized.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Zed Seven services or websites you visit.

**Security of your Personal Information**  
To secure your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure, Zed Seven uses the following:

[WPEngine](https://www.associateprograms.com/wpengine "WPEngine.com").com

**Children Under Thirteen**  
Zed Seven does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen. If you are under the age of thirteen, you must ask your parent or guardian for permission to use this website.

**Disconnecting your Zed Seven Account from Third Party Websites**  
You will be able to connect your Zed Seven account to third party accounts. BY CONNECTING YOUR ZED SEVEN ACCOUNT TO YOUR THIRD PARTY ACCOUNT, YOU ACKNOWLEDGE AND AGREE THAT YOU ARE CONSENTING TO THE CONTINUOUS RELEASE OF INFORMATION ABOUT YOU TO OTHERS (IN ACCORDANCE WITH YOUR PRIVACY SETTINGS ON THOSE THIRD PARTY SITES). IF YOU DO NOT WANT INFORMATION ABOUT YOU, INCLUDING PERSONALLY IDENTIFYING INFORMATION, TO BE SHARED INTHIS MANNER, DO NOT USE THE THIS FEATURE. You may disconnect your account from a third party account at any time. Users may disconnect their accounts from third-party websites by visiting those 3rd parties and revoking access..

**Opt-Out & Unsubscribe**  
We respect your privacy and give you an opportunity to opt-out of receiving announcements of certain information. Users may opt-out of receiving any or all communications from Zed Seven by contacting us here:

– Clicking unsubscribe in the footer of all emails.  
– Email: help@zedseven.com.au

**Changes to this Statement**  
Zed Seven will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. Zed Seven encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how Zed Seven is protecting your information.

**Contact Information**  
Zed Seven welcomes your questions or comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that Zed Seven has not adhered to this Statement, please contact Zed Seven at:

Zed Seven Pty Ltd ATF The Stockwell Family Trust  
PO Box 1196  
Burleigh Heads, Qld 2486

Email Address:  
help@zedseven.com.au

_________________

Effective as of May 04, 2014

Apr 8, 2009
